After we have hit the roots on our 4 sections, we are going to let that sit for another 20 minutes.
Now about the last 5-10 minutes of your application what you are going to want to do is you are going to be breaking the color line.
So you are going to be kind of blending it.
So what you can do is go through sections, maybe about a inch instead of a quarter inch take bigger sections.
Gently comb it through, all the way through your ends.
Another one inch section taking it from the root and gently just pulling it through and combing it through your ends.
You want to remember not to irritate the scalp so just gently graze the scalp as you are bring the comb through your ends.
Set it aside.
1 inch section, comb it through, and set it aside.
You are going to go through all 4 sections doing this combing through and we would go on to our next section.